I came here
我来这里
okay
好的
welcome to blockchain aetherium and
欢迎来到区块链以太坊
business applications my name is
商业应用程序我叫
Matthias I'm working for psi Switzerland
Matthias我为psi瑞士工作
I'm one of the project leads of the
我是该项目的项目负责人之一
eclipse cow project you're going to hear
月食牛项目，您将听到
about what we've learned during the last
关于上次学到的东西
year by exploring the blockchain domain
探索区块链领域的一年
at work
工作中
so basically you probably have heard of
所以基本上你可能听说过
Bitcoin or Orissa via magic tons of
比特币或奥里萨邦通过魔术吨
other cryptocurrencies as well there's a
其他加密货币以及
lot of money involved which means that
涉及很多钱，这意味着
many many individuals see now their
现在很多人看到他们的
point in time to start the startup so if
准时开始启动，所以如果
you if you have blockchain startup in
如果您有区块链启动
Google landscape you get tons of small
谷歌风景，你得到吨的小
images each one is a logo each one is
图像每个是一个徽标每个是
connected to a hope of a particular
与特定的希望有关
session or a person to get rich quickly
会议或一个人快速致富
if you're an organization then this is
如果您是一个组织，那么这是
my this might not be the good approach
我的这可能不是一个好方法
but what these guys do you build an
但是你会用这些家伙建立一个
alliance or you train alliance so it's
联盟或您训练联盟，所以
similar to IOT when you realize that
当您意识到与物联网类似时
something big is happening and you start
大事情正在发生，你开始
to to to be anxious that you miss the
要担心你错过了
train so there's a lot of that stuff
训练所以有很多东西
going on right now
现在继续
and recently there even popped up
最近又出现了
something like a crypto Valiant which is
像加密货币英勇之类的东西是
catering for our project community and
为我们的项目社区服务
contrary to its coaches called the
与教练所说的相反
valley in the blockchain domain but
区块链领域的山谷，但是
however it's not located where you
但是它不在你的位置
probably would expect it instead it's
可能会期望它相反
located in the center of Europe in the
位于欧洲中部
centre of Switzerland close to a really
瑞士中心靠近一个真正的
small sleepy town sooo which I grew up
我长大的困小镇
it's kind of funny and so basically
这很有趣，所以基本上
between so cancer ik now this small town
之间如此癌症ik现在这个小镇
is getting less sleepy by the year
到一年前变得越来越困
because of all this hype so how much
因为这么大肆宣传
money is there we can compare a number
钱在那里，我们可以比较一个数字
of the top cryptocurrencies the bitcoin
顶级加密货币中的比特币
III Omaha and some others if we look for
III奥马哈和其他一些如果我们寻找
for Bitcoin this is approaching 100
对于比特币，这已经接近100
billion us the total capitalization of
亿美元，
the word which basically is around the
这个词基本上是围绕
GDP of a country
一个国家的GDP
like Trisha cerium is on the assert
就像Trisha铈一样
which is around the GDP of a country of
大约是一个国家的GDP
Cyprus so all of this money is creating
塞浦路斯，所有这些钱都在创造
a lot of excitement and this case the
很兴奋，这种情况下
situation where many many people start
很多人开始的情况
to to get into blockchain but what they
进入区块链，但他们
actually mean they're just afraid to
其实意味着他们只是害怕
miss the money train so they're really
想念钱火车，所以他们真的
interested when to buy and when to sell
有兴趣何时购买和何时出售
and all the stuff and not so many people
和所有的东西，没有那么多人
already interested and understanding
已经有兴趣和理解
concepts behind blockchain which are
区块链背后的概念是
really really necessary if you want to
如果你想真的很必要
charge you something as married or not
指控您已婚或未婚
being special as a developer of course
作为开发者当然很特别
and being at the development conference
并参加开发会议
you're not going to do this thing but
你不会做这个事情，但是
rather please say so let's move towards
而是请说，让我们继续前进
understanding Bitcoin first why Bitcoin
首先了解比特币，为什么比特币
it's just historically because Bitcoin
这只是历史原因，因为比特币
has been the first implementation of a
是第一个实施
successful blockchain and since it was
成功的区块链，因为它是
created by a guy or a girl Satoshi
由男孩或女孩Satoshi创建
nakamoto's the question mark is because
中本问号是因为
we don't even know if it was a single
我们甚至不知道这是否是一个
person or group of small persons so it's
一个人或一群小人，所以
100 billion is running on an
1000亿美元正在运行
infrastructure initially created by
最初由以下人员创建的基础结构
somebody we don't even know it became
一个我们甚至都不知道的人
open-source software in 2009 so let's
2009年的开源软件，让我们
assume that we have one of these Bitcoin
假设我们有这些比特币之一
wallets on on a map and we go into a
在地图上的钱包，我们进入
coffee and the coffee happens to accept
咖啡和咖啡碰巧接受
Bitcoin to pay your coffee so what you
比特币支付您的咖啡，所以您
do at when you pay for the coffee you
当您支付咖啡费用时
get a QR code inside of the QR code you
在您的QR码中获取QR码
can scan that with your mobile wallet
可以用您的手机钱包进行扫描
and their metadata encrypted or in
及其元数据加密或加密
encoding the QR code for example the
编码QR码，例如
address where the money is going to and
解决钱去哪儿的问题
that amount of bitcoins that you way to
您要使用的比特币数量
pay for that coffee that coffee would
付那咖啡要的咖啡
never be so expensive because the
永远不会那么昂贵，因为
example comes out of this book and pick
例子来自本书
one has exploded in value so you
一个已经爆炸了价值，所以你
probably never paid
可能从未付款
much will cover these days so for this
这些天将覆盖很多，因此
addresses what what is this actually
解决这实际上是什么
it's basically a form of accounts so if
这基本上是一种帐户形式，所以如果
you have traditional accounts or funds
您有传统帐户或资金
in the fortune world you have addresses
在财富世界中，您有住所
in the case of Bitcoin it's just an
在比特币的情况下，
encoded number and that number is
编码的号码，那个号码是
derived from a public public private
源自公共机构
keeper so how do I get these addresses
老板，所以我怎么获得这些地址
how can I use it and maybe lose it to
我该如何使用它，甚至可能失去它
get your address basically to accumulate
得到你的地址基本上是积累
funds and then spend it you don't need
资金然后花掉你不需要的
to ask anyone you just create your
问问你刚创建的人
private key person to derive the address
私钥人得出地址
from that and you're done so there's no
从那，你就完成了，所以没有
ID required no showing up at the local
身份证号必须不显示在本地
branch well there is even a local branch
分行很好，甚至还有本地分行
to show up to send bitcoins once you
出现以发送比特币
have some funds under your address and
您的地址下面有一些资金，
you want to transfer those funds to
您想将这些资金转移到
somebody else you need your private key
别人，你需要你的私钥
because you need the private key to sign
因为您需要私钥进行签名
the transaction that it's okay for some
对某些人来说还可以的交易
funds to move to the target address that
资金转移到目标地址
you will designate it as a recipient
您将其指定为收件人
this also implies that it's not good
这也意味着它不好
losing private keys because if you lose
丢失私钥，因为如果丢失
the private key you can look at your
您可以查看您的私钥
account you can see how much money there
帐户，您可以看到那里有多少钱
is but there's no way how you can access
是，但无法访问
the fund or transfer to somebody else
资金或转移给其他人
basically the bitcoins are locked into
基本上，比特币被锁定
that account or they become worthless so
该帐户或他们变得一文不值，所以
the border to towards a Bitcoin network
通往比特币网络的边界
what you have seen you have a a mobile
您所看到的，您拥有一部手机
wallet or a desktop or whatever that is
钱包或台式机或其他任何东西
usually connected to a Bitcoin client
通常连接到比特币客户端
the Bitcoin client is responsible to sin
比特币客户有责任犯罪
and silence actions to the network it
并让网络静音动作
mines new blocks we'll come to that in a
挖掘新的块，我们将在
minute
分钟
and this is really important all the
这真的很重要
local copy of the blockchain so that
区块链的本地副本
client that you have is connected in a
您拥有的客户端已连接到
peer-to-peer fashion to all the clients
所有客户的点对点时尚
and this whole thing together around the
和这整个事情一起
globe is for me the Bitcoin network so
地球对我来说是比特币网络，所以
each of these circles has a local copy
每个圈子都有一个本地副本
of the complete blockchain which means
完整的区块链的意思
each transactions from the inception of
从开始的每个交易
Bitcoin until today is stored in this
直到今天的比特币都存储在此
whole global PPO network so it becomes
整个全球PPO网络，因此它成为
obvious that you can kill many of these
很明显，您可以杀死其中许多
or even if you manage to do that you
甚至即使您设法做到这一点
will not manage your shot count to shut
将无法管理您的镜头计数
down the network because basically you
在网络上，因为基本上你
can recreate
可以重新创建
the whole network even from a single
整个网络甚至从一个单一的
node if if that's an extreme case but
节点，如果这是一个极端的情况，但
it's you're thinking possible so these
是你在想可能所以这些
contractions if you sent a transaction
收缩（如果您发送交易）
it is all caught on confirmed
这一切都被确认
transaction and that is spread through
交易，并通过传播
the network
网络
I hope my long connections okay so we
我希望我的长久联系可以，所以我们
can actually look at that in real life
可以在现实生活中看到
so this is a a blockchain Explorer for
所以这是一个区块链资源管理器
the Bitcoin network and here you see the
比特币网络，在这里您可以看到
live unconfirmed transactions from the
来自未确认的未确认交易
globe coming in so that H is connected
地球进入以便H连接
to a bit covenant from their node and
从他们的节点有点盟约
from there it you see all that
从那里你可以看到所有
information currently the thing is
目前信息是
around four transactions per second
大约每秒四笔交易
which is a bit more than half of the
这是一半以上的
capacity of the global Bitcoin network
全球比特币网络的容量
so let's move back to the slides so the
所以让我们回到幻灯片上
coffee transaction what what is it
咖啡交易是什么
this is from the same table train
这是同一班火车
Explorer you have the address where
资源管理器中您的地址在哪里
you're sending the phones from me of the
您正在从我那里发送电话
address re send it to there's a coffee
地址重新发送到那里喝咖啡
price there's a return money that goes
价格有回本钱
to your own address again and there is a
再到您自己的地址，有一个
small thing which is called transaction
小东西，叫做交易
fee so you have to pay for the fact that
费用，所以您必须支付以下费用
you're actually running the transaction
您实际上正在执行交易
and really important there's a link to
真的很重要
transaction block so if if Bob's coffee
交易阻塞，如果鲍勃的咖啡
is really fairly easy going when they
当他们真的很随和
see the transaction coming as the
看到交易即将到来
unconfirmed accent they can say have
他们可以说有未经确认的口音
your coffee if there are more cautious
你的咖啡如果比较谨慎
they say no no I want to see the
他们说不不，我想看看
transaction in the block first if
如果块中的交易先
they're really picky they say well you
他们真的很挑剔他们说的很好
know there might be a competing
知道可能会有竞争
sidechain I wait until I have a couple
等到我有一对夫妻
of blocks on top of that and only then I
除此之外，只有我
believe that the money is actually mine
相信这笔钱实际上是我的
this leads to a situation or if you just
这会导致某种情况，或者如果您只是
wait for the first block usually it's
等待第一个街区通常是
supposed to be inside of the block is in
应该在街区里面
ten minutes what that can really take
十分钟真正需要的时间
hours depending on the congestion of the
小时，取决于交通拥堵
Bitcoin network even small transactions
比特币网络甚至很小的交易
can can take many many hours until
可能要花很多小时才能
they're confirmed so there's a huge
他们已经确认，所以有一个巨大的
backlog probably this is not often but
积压可能不经常
sometimes it is the case that the
有时情况是
network is not really flush if you want
如果您想要的话，网络并不是真的很红
so this transaction is a reset in a
因此，此交易是在
block let's look at what what a block is
块让我们看看什么是块
it has a block number and it has a
它有一个块号，并且有一个
number of transactions inside of that
其中的交易数量
block and there's a block hash in the
块中有一个块哈希
block hash is just a long number the
块哈希只是一个长数字
funny things there's a ton of of initial
有趣的事情有很多的初始
zeros we'll come to that in a minute
零，我们将在一分钟内得出结论
really important also there's a link to
真的很重要，还有一个链接
the hash of the previous block basically
基本上前一个块的哈希
this block is our transaction is linked
这个区块是我们的交易被链接
to the block with other transactions
与其他交易一起进入区块
before and that before and so on we get
之前和之前，等等
to block number one which is called the
阻止被称为
Genesis block and because of all this
创世块，因为所有这些
construction the whole technology is
建设整个技术是
called blockchain so how do we come from
叫做区块链，那么我们怎么来
a transaction to a block basically this
交易到块基本上是这个
is the the mining game we have seen that
是我们看到的采矿游戏
you have transactions that are
你有交易
unconfirmed and propagated through the
未经确认并通过
Bitcoin network the client receives
客户收到的比特币网络
these transactions such as similar as we
这些交易，例如我们
have seen in the web page and if enough
在网页上看过，如果足够的话
transactions are there the client can
客户可以在那里进行交易
start to mine
开始开采
what what does it mean basically the
基本上是什么意思
client has a pool where you can pull out
客户有一个游泳池，你可以拉出来
unconfirmed transactions put them in a
未经确认的交易将其放入
pool and say this is my block candidate
池，说这是我的阻止候选人
and now I'm going to solve the block
现在我要解决这个问题
candidates crypto challenge when the
候选人加密挑战赛
client has solved that challenge first
客户首先解决了这个挑战
when it's the first guy that has
当它是第一个拥有
basically solved the new block if you
基本上解决了新的障碍
want he gets a block reward which is
希望他获得块奖励
basically fresh freshly peeled freshly
基本上新鲜新鲜剥皮
printed bitcoins and the client also
印刷比特币，客户也
gets all the transaction fees that that
得到所有的交易费用
belong to the unconfirmed transactions
属于未确认交易
which is basically incentive for the
这基本上是对
client to first take the transactions
客户首先接受交易
that have high transaction fees and is
交易费用很高，并且
get usually processed faster however
通常得到更快的处理
when you get is a lock you extend it to
当您获得锁时，将其扩展到
your peers but that's not the normal
你的同龄人，但这不是正常的
case the normal cases you actually
正常情况下
receive the block from somebody else and
从别人那里收到块
that guy did win all the money not you
那家伙确实赢了所有钱，不是你
this means that you can throw away
这意味着你可以扔掉
whatever you've been doing and you start
不管你在做什么然后开始
to race over at the tree basically you
基本上是在树上竞跑
have to read
必须阅读
a new one with new transactions and then
新交易的新交易，然后
you can start the game again so let's
您可以再次开始游戏，所以让我们
look at the descriptive challenge the
看看描述性的挑战
trick is that we have seen there's a
诀窍是，我们已经看到有一个
pointer to the to the hash of the
指向的哈希值的指针
previous block which is basically this
前一块基本上是这个
number here it's just added the time
这里的数字只是加上时间
implementation then there's a section
实现，然后有一个部分
which is just sent here which is the
刚刚发送到这里是
payload here let's go all the
有效负载在这里，让我们去所有
transactions that you decided to put
您决定进行的交易
into next block and there is a small
进入下一个街区，有一个小
portion of data that just random noise
只是随机噪声的数据部分
and then the challenge goes us that you
然后我们面临的挑战是
have to compute the hash over the whole
必须计算整个哈希
string which gives some number and you
给出一些数字的字符串，你
repeat that until you get leading zeroes
重复这一过程，直到得到零
in that case if the difficulty of the
在这种情况下，如果
network is to have a single leading 0
网络应具有单个前导0
then you don't need to do so so many
那你就不需要那么多
experiments is randomizing this part in
实验正在将该部分随机化
that case in this example the equipment
在这个例子中，设备
had to run 29 of these guys if if you
如果你要的话，必须跑29个家伙
increase the difficulty to let side for
加大让步的难度
leading zeroes it gets more complicated
前导零变得更加复杂
and it needs actually to compute 11,500
它实际上需要计算11,500
hashes to have the first instance before
散列之前具有第一实例
leading zeroes in the real Bitcoin
在真正的比特币中领先零
network right now if you do the hashing
如果您执行哈希操作，现在就联网
you need 18 leading zeros and forgets to
您需要18个前导零，而忘记了
compute something like that on a normal
在法线上计算出类似的结果
machine even on a GPU you have to have
机器甚至必须在GPU上
special special purpose hardware to do
特殊用途的特殊硬件
that and the second one doesn't really
那和第二个不是真的
help you have to assign that to a pool
帮助您必须将其分配给池
or you have to have many of them and
或者你必须有很多
only then it really starts to make sense
才真正开始有意义
to participate in the game of mining and
参加采矿和
getting money out of the mining so it
从采矿中赚钱，所以
kept recap it's a completely the central
不断回顾，这完全是中央
currency so there's no need for banks
货币，因此不需要银行
especially if there's no need for a
特别是如果不需要
central bank because the network is
中央银行，因为网络是
printing its own money it's open source
印刷自己的钱，它是开源的
and github you can also say it's open
和github你也可以说它是开放的
data because each client has access to
数据，因为每个客户端都可以访问
all the transactions completely open and
所有交易完全开放，
it's a perfect restful implementation of
这是一个完美的宁静实现
any cryptocurrency or any block or chain
任何加密货币或任何区块链
instance it's basically the gold
基本上是黄金
standard since 2009 has never been
自2009年以来从未有过的标准
hacked since 2009 and this year
自2009年以来被黑客入侵，今年
especially there
特别是那里
price levels for the see the current
价格水平为当前
challenges or the ongoing scaling the
挑战或持续扩展
peignoir as you have seen before max
如您在max之前所见
capacity of Bitcoin at 47 transactions
47次交易时比特币的容量
per second which is kind of ridiculous
每秒，这有点荒谬
if you compare tool to visa but still
如果您将工具与签证进行比较，但仍然
it's working that they're working on it
他们正在为此而努力
eventually to find solutions and there's
最终找到解决方案，
also declining market share that is not
也减少了不小的市场份额
necessarily bad because why is that
一定不好，因为那是为什么
there are successful competitions from a
有成功的比赛
cerium or Forex of Bitcoin and many many
铈或比特币的外汇和许多
others if you want to learn more
其他如果您想了解更多
resources you can read the right paper
您可以阅读正确论文的资源
that's online available you can browse
这是在线可用的，您可以浏览
the Bitcoin core client on github you
github上的比特币核心客户端
can a book this is highly recommended
可以推荐这本书吗
this is either you can buy it in the
这是要么你可以在购买
shop or you can download for free and
商店，或者您可以免费下载和
also the book is on Paquito it's using
这本书也在Paquito上使用
ask a doctor so you're even open to
问医生，所以你甚至愿意
contribute to to the book if you find
如果您发现这本书有助于
anything that is missing now let's move
现在缺少的东西让我们继续前进
to the cerium this is not only a
到铈这不仅是
currency but it also contains the
货币，但也包含
concept of smart contracts and this is
智能合约的概念，这是
the focus of what we're going to look at
我们要看的重点
it was created by a guy called metallic
它是由一个叫做metallic的家伙创建的
tutoring and he was really into Bitcoin
补习，他真的很喜欢比特币
first so he had a really really thorough
首先，他有一个非常非常彻底的
understanding of the Bitcoin technology
对比特币技术的了解
before he came out with business serum
在他拿出商业精华素之前
it includes a distributed virtual
它包括一个分布式虚拟
machine which is Turing complete and
图灵完整的机器，
that is interesting because for the
这很有趣，因为对于
smart contracts and he just copied the
智能合约，他只是复制了
schema and he was open source which
模式，他是开源的
basically created this situation that
基本上造成了这种情况
you can no longer create or even think
您无法再创建甚至思考
about creating a blockchain technology
关于创建区块链技术
without having that open source so it's
没有那个开源，所以
not optional to be an open source domain
不能作为开放源域
it's actually mandatory so if you
这实际上是强制性的，所以如果您
compare the serum and fitco and so for
比较血清和fitco，等等
common traits is a virtual currency it
共同特征是一种虚拟货币
has a peer-to-peer network there the
那里有一个对等网络
concepts of addresses transactions
地址交易的概念
mining so I can skip that and win that's
挖矿，所以我可以跳过并赢得那
not small differences but the conceptual
不小的差异，但概念上
part is actually the same the main
主要部分实际上是相同的
differences is a theorem is
差异是一个定理是
specification driven so there's a
规范驱动，所以有一个
specification for the a serum client
血清客户规范
which leads to a number of competing
这导致了许多竞争
mutation whereas in Bitcoin there's a
突变，而在比特币中有一个
Bitcoin core reference implementation
比特币核心参考实现
you sometimes have a hard time to create
您有时很难创建
something that could compete with that
可以与之竞争的东西
the next difference is smart contracts
下一个区别是智能合约
and including the serum virtual machine
并包括血清虚拟机
and the concept of gas which is kind of
气体的概念
special so this is the reason why we go
很特别，所以这就是我们走的原因
to look at gas
看气
what is this basically it's unit to pay
这基本上是多少钱？
the mining notes basically the unit that
采矿基本上记录了
you pay the notes which is incentive
你付钱是激励
that they actually running the notes
他们实际上在运行笔记
unit of gas has a price in either's so
单位汽油的价格是
basically you pay some either's you get
基本上你付一些就可以
a number of turns and with that you can
几圈，这样你就可以
do stuff what can you do you can pay
做东西你能做什么你可以付钱
transaction fees but you also can't pay
交易费，但您也无法支付
for the solution of smart contracts
用于智能合约的解决方案
basically you pay for the computations
基本上你为计算付费
that are performed on the resilient
在弹性上执行
virtual machine on the clients the trick
虚拟机在客户端上的把戏
is that the eye serum virtual machine is
是眼睛血清虚拟机是
working as long as there is gas so if if
只要有气就工作，如果
you provide gas to the IBM and say do
您向IBM提供天然气并说服
this if you happily start and if you if
如果你快乐地开始，如果你
you gave enough then we will complete if
你给了足够的钱，那么我们将完成
you don't give enough it does not
你给的不够，那不会
complete for example to compute that a
例如完成计算
hash that this is fixed it costs 330 gas
哈希，这是固定的，需要花费330汽油
and this is a termination thing which is
这是一个终结的东西
called a cool concept it makes sure that
这个很酷的概念可以确保
the Roth machine always terminates
罗斯机器总是会终止
whatever the program will do so
不管程序会这样做
basically if if you're dumb enough to
基本上，如果你足够傻
create an endless loop or if you don't
创建一个无限循环，否则
really do good software it means that if
真正做得很好的软件意味着
you click it on you provide gas the ECM
您单击它就可以提供ECM气体
is EBM is running and at some point
EBM正在运行，并且在某个时候
there's no more gas
不再有汽油
so they will just abort this means you
所以他们只会中止这意味着你
transaction did not complete but you got
交易未完成，但是您得到了
rid of your money this is a good
摆脱你的钱，这是一个很好的
incentive to write good code and compact
编写好的代码和紧凑的动机
code ok smart contracts what is that
代码确定智能合约是什么
basically it's a code written in a
基本上是用
high-level language usually these days
这些天通常是高级语言
it's most in solidity and that code is
这是最可靠的，而代码是
then compiled into a byte code which can
然后编译成一个字节码
be run on the ECM virtual machine it has
在它拥有的ECM虚拟机上运行
an owner a smart contract it has an
所有者拥有智能合约
address when deployed each smart
部署每个智能设备时的地址
contract has an address and having in
合同有地址并且有
others we're again at the point where
其他人，我们再次处于
and others can hold money so basically
其他人基本上可以持有货币
it can hold current
它可以保持电流
basically this means that the contract
基本上这意味着合同
itself distributed the blockchain is the
本身分布的区块链是
owner of the money so even if you deploy
资金的所有者，因此即使您进行部署
money there it does not mean that you
那里的钱并不意味着你
can access that money it's only the
可以使用那笔钱，这仅仅是
contract that can really access that
可以真正访问的合同
money of course you can write code that
钱当然可以写代码
if you trigger the code it gives money
如果您触发代码，它就会赚钱
back to you
回到你身边
example two one is slightly like
示例二一个有点像
insurance the second one is a truly
保险第二个是真正的
autonomous car slightly lay-up which is
自动驾驶汽车稍稍上铺
now life because there's a some
现在的生活，因为有一些
conference going on in Cancun so they
会议在坎昆举行，所以他们
typically manage to do also the
通常设法做到
regulatory part so this is a fully liens
监管部分，所以这是完全留置权
license thing that you can enter some
您可以输入一些许可的东西
your your name fight detail stuff then
你的名字打细节的话
you can say over to insure my plight for
你可以说一遍以确保我的困境
example you you move here 35 for 25
例如，您在这里移动35表示25
euros and there's some payout scheme if
欧元，如果有一些支付计划，
you fly this delayed by 30 minutes you
你把这个延误了30分钟
get eighty two years back how does it
回来八十二年了
work
工作
it takes advantage of a of another
它利用了另一个的优势
webpage which this is called flights
称为航班的网页
let's calm this is real-time information
让我们冷静一下，这是实时信息
for all the flights going on if they
对于所有正在进行的航班
learn when they're supposed to land by
学习何时应该降落
looking at historic data you can
查看历史数据，您可以
calculate how likely it is the specific
计算具体可能性
flight is going to be late
航班要晚了
this helps you to for risk modeling and
这可以帮助您进行风险建模和
based on that data that condition here
根据这里条件的数据
is in captured in the smart contract and
被捕获在智能合约中
by accessing at the right moment the
在适当的时候访问
smart contract can pay at you without
智能合约可以不付钱给您
human intervention just looks to this
人为干预只是看这个
loosely thing usually smart contracts
松散的东西通常是智能合约
cannot look outside of itself so how the
不能看向自己的外部，所以
link is done is a piece of code that is
链接完成是一段代码
called or or applies library what it
叫或应用图书馆什么
does is basically it allows you to
基本上是可以让您
access information through specific
通过特定的访问信息
pages it makes sure that if you rely on
页面可以确保您依赖
that information
该信息
nobody did tamper with with that
没有人干预
information which makes it it's not
信息使它不是
complete trust in the blockchain it out
完全信任区块链
sources apart but it it's mostly good
资料来源分开，但大部分都很好
for many many use cases basically you
对于许多许多用例，基本上
could attack that smart contract only by
只能通过以下方式攻击该智能合约
hacking flight status
骇客飞行状态
this is I think white pine Isle of
这是我认为的白松岛
services or by completely hacking what
服务或完全黑客入侵
they do then you can make sure that you
他们那么你可以确保你
get more money than everything else but
得到的钱比其他任何东西都要多，但是
this this I think this combination
这个我觉得这个组合
between our clients and a serum this
在我们的客户和血清之间
will even become pretty big so next
甚至会变得很大，所以接下来
example truly autonomous cars you have
例如您拥有的真正的自动驾驶汽车
been getting used to autonomous cars to
习惯了自动驾驶汽车
drive around it only to drive but
绕着它开车，但是
there's a nice combination in Germany
在德国有一个很好的组合
this year the RWD they introduced a
今年的RWD，他们推出了
charging stations which are connected to
连接到的充电站
the blockchain basically to pay for for
基本上要支付的区块链
your currency you can move the users
您的货币，您可以移动用户
over there and you get the right to to
在那边，您有权
load your battery this means that you
装入电池，这意味着您
can add a smart contract for the car and
可以为汽车添加智能合约，并且
you can do other things so basically if
你基本上可以做其他事情，如果
you order that autonomous car you move
您订购自动挡汽车
some funds to the car contract and you
汽车合同的一些资金，你
sell very over just check us the car to
卖完了就给我们买车
come to your place and pick you up so
到你家来接你
the car can you accumulate funds with
这辆车你可以用
these funds the car can do stuff the car
这些资金可以为汽车做些东西
can do pay for energy over here it could
可以为此付出能源
also make a competition to be cleaned so
也要比赛要清洗
it can include for example business are
它可以包括例如业务
you if you the lowest bidder the car
你，如果你出价最低的车
will come to you and you flip the car
会来找你，你把车翻转
something like that
这样的东西
okay from this high-level examples let's
从这些高级示例中可以，让我们
go to hello world first you to take
首先去你好世界
greeter mr. factory JavaScript library
迎宾先生工厂JavaScript库
and works like that you have seen this
就像你看到的那样
example here in Bitcoin cash in the
此处以比特币现金为例
theorem case you have not a Bitcoin
定理情况下你没有比特币
client of the serum client we have seen
我们见过的血清客户的客户
that there's a specification the typical
有一个规范，典型的
client most people are using is the gas
大多数人使用的客户是天然气
client which is written will go but
被写的客户会去但是
there's also JavaScript client which is
还有一个JavaScript客户端
called test art RTC while tests are PC
在PC上进行测试时称为测试艺术RTC
because they simulate the blockchain in
因为他们在
memory which is really useful if you
记忆，如果你真的很有用
want to write unit tests against that
想要针对此编写单元测试
stuff and it has an interface which is a
东西，它有一个接口是
JSON RPC interface available on under
JSON RPC接口可在下面找到
under the support and there is a
在支持下，有一个
JavaScript library called lab 3 that we
我们称为实验3的JavaScript库
are going to see in a minute and there's
一分钟后就会看到
also a web search a library which you
还可以通过网络搜索您所需要的图书馆
can use when your integer
可以使用您的整数时
so basically in the hello world this is
所以基本上在你好世界
solidity code it's a contract creature
坚固性代码，它是一种契约生物
the contract has an owner that we want
合同有我们想要的所有者
to remember there's a strain for if you
要记住，如果你
create a new contract you run through
创建您运行的新合同
tis a constructor you say you want to
这是您说要构造的
provide discrete thing and the first
提供离散的东西和第一个
thing it does it's remembering who is
要做的事情就是记住谁是
triggering this transaction and with
触发此交易并
each transaction you know who the sender
您知道每笔交易的发件人
of the transaction was so here you can
交易是这样的，在这里你可以
remember who the owner was
记得主人是谁
this is important we'll see this in a
这很重要，我们将在
minute there's a main function creat it
分钟，有一个主要功能创建它
just returns for 12 of these provided
仅返回其中提供的12个
when we created contract and there's a
当我们创建合同时，有一个
function kill and it's killed you can
功能杀死，它可以杀死
basically kill the smart contract this
基本上杀死了智能合约
is a means of cleaning up after yourself
是一种清理自己的手段
so you don't contrast the blockchain
所以你不用对比区块链
with with stuff that is long obsolete
与已经过时的东西
we have heard before that the contract
我们之前听说过合同
can hold money and you cannot access the
可以持有货币，而您无法访问
money so how do we get the money
钱，那我们怎么得到钱
assuming that you wanna kill your
假设你想杀死你的
contract you want the money back you
合同，你要钱还给你
have to implement the skill function if
必须执行技能功能
you don't implement then the money if
你不执行那么钱
the stock so you have to do that but
库存，所以您必须这样做，但是
anybody can call that kill method so you
任何人都可以调用该kill方法，因此您
want to make sure that if you're the
要确保如果您是
owner of the contract only you can have
只有您可以拥有的合同所有者
the possibility to kill and get the
杀死并获得
funds which is basically this is if the
资金基本上就是如果
sender is the owner that you you
发件人是您的所有者
registered here in the constructor then
然后在构造函数中注册此处
your ownself construct and in that case
您自己的构造，在这种情况下
the contract itself is mostly all the
合同本身大部分是
funds of it hands to the owner address
资金转交给业主地址
of the contract as long as you don't do
合同，只要你不做
this you cannot directly access lab
您无法直接访问实验室
monies small extension there such as a
钱小扩展那里，如
integer or for number of deposits and
整数或存款数，以及
the special the default function which
特殊的默认功能
has the keyboard payable if you want to
如果您想支付键盘费用
move money to a contract you need to
将资金转移到您需要的合同上
have at least one function with this
至少具有一项功能
payable and only by column is function
应付帐款，仅按列即可
you can you can start to move funds to
您可以开始将资金转移到
that contract and that's just basically
那个合同，那基本上是
accessing the number of deposits on to
访问上的存款数量
once you have this piece of source code
一旦有了这段源代码
you need a solidity compiler
你需要一个坚固的编译器
one is online available which is pretty
一个在线可用，很漂亮
neat you copy/paste the source code over
整洁地复制/粘贴源代码
here it compiles and you get out the ID
在这里编译，您得到ID
code
码
over here you also get some interface
在这里，您还可以获得一些界面
string which also need and it shows you
还需要的字符串，它告诉你
thing where you can actually deploy it's
可以实际部署的地方是
a very gems JavaScript likely to to the
一个非常珍贵的JavaScript，可能
blockchain and this is all said deploy
区块链，这一切都说部署
script so if you're in a shell and you
脚本，所以如果您在外壳中并且
have the web tree JavaScript library
拥有网络树JavaScript库
loaded you can use that script to
加载后，您可以使用该脚本来
basically to deploy the contract and to
基本上是部署合同并
do stuff if you successfully deploy
如果成功部署，则可以进行操作
you'll get back the contact address so
您将获得联系地址，以便
you know when you're in the blockchain
你知道当你在区块链中时
your contract is living and by calling
您的合同有效并通过致电
Rita Creech you see hello world so
丽塔·克里奇（Rita Creech）
success that that will work on let's
可以成功的成功让我们
move to the Java space and do basically
转移到Java空间并基本上完成
the same for we have seen that pasties
同样，因为我们已经看到了馅饼
are simply chase an interface a guy
只是追逐一个家伙的界面
decided to do this for travel as well
决定也这样做旅行
not only JavaScript this is the home
不只是JavaScript，这就是家
page of that thing and if you have
页面的东西，如果你有
initially the binary code and the of a
最初的二进制代码和
basis is interface string you can use a
基础是接口字符串，您可以使用
command line tool to create or to
命令行工具来创建或
generate the green tea Java which you
生成您所用的绿茶Java
can then just used to work with Miss not
然后就可以和小姐一起工作了
likely let's look at this individual in
可能让我们看看这个人
the demo so basically this is small
演示所以基本上这很小
contracts demo there's an address called
合同演示有一个称为
Alice so we move some phones to Alice
爱丽丝，所以我们将一些电话移到爱丽丝
then you can deploy the contract so
然后您可以部署合同，这样
Alice's standard the owner of that
爱丽丝的标准所有者
contract and using that contract there's
合同并使用该合同
a method that move some money over there
一种将钱转移到那的方法
we call green tentacle the contract I
我们称绿色触手为合同我
can run this as just a normal
可以正常运行
application and it's like if and he did
申请，就像，如果他做了
all that stuff and it's so quick because
所有的东西，它是如此之快，因为
it did run against test RPC if you would
如果您愿意，它确实针对测试RPC运行
run this against a lifetime of this
以此为生
theorem this would take a minute or two
定理这需要一两分钟
so it's really cool for though you can
所以虽然可以
really do Ju any tests by by shooting
通过射击真的可以进行任何测试
against these tests or PC library
针对这些测试或PC库
so let's do a slightly more extensive
所以让我们做一个更广泛的
demo which is the trading network demo a
演示这是交易网络演示a
use case is currency hatching you want
用例是您想要的货币孵化
to manage buy and sell orders for your
管理您的买卖订单
against us basically it's a classical
基本上对我们来说是经典
business application why do we need a
商业应用程序为什么我们需要一个
business application or whatever if you
商业应用程序或其他（如果您使用）
have startups or whatever you you
有初创公司或任何你
usually need to do some identity
通常需要做一些身份
magnitude we see now that more and more
数量，我们现在看到越来越多
of this sort of minute block chain space
这种微小的区块链空间
they they realize that they have to take
他们意识到必须采取
seriously things like money laundering
认真地洗钱
so they have to do a ml and they have to
所以他们必须做一毫升，他们必须
know your customer so they're slowly
了解您的客户，所以他们很慢
adding even before the regulations
甚至在法规之前添加
completely here I start to add this
完全在这里，我开始添加这个
stuff because they get afraid if they
东西，因为他们害怕如果他们
don't do they will be shot down too
否则他们也会被击落
early it also includes the web DJ
早期还包括网络DJ
library and I could schedule to build
图书馆，我可以安排建造
basically the application around it so
基本上围绕它的应用程序
the benefits of using to blockchain is
使用区块链的好处是
efficiency efficiency in the sense that
效率效率
if you do this is hatching game usually
如果您这样做通常是孵化游戏
there are many organizations involved
有很多组织参与
which do not necessarily trust each
不一定彼此信任
other if you do this is classical
其他，如果你这样做是古典的
infrastructure you are usually forced to
通常被迫使用的基础架构
set up an independent organization where
建立一个独立的组织
the participant or the organization they
参与者或他们的组织
trust that they don't mess up and the
相信他们不会搞砸，并且
trick is blockchain is that you can
诀窍是区块链是你可以
delete the independent organization you
删除您的独立组织
don't need so you don't need housing you
不需要，所以您不需要住房
don't need Emperor you sit on it almost
不需要皇帝，您几乎可以坐在上面
nothing which was used for the trust
没有用于信托的东西
part you can use the blockchain because
您可以使用区块链的一部分，因为
option is offering with tampering proof
选项提供防篡改证明
lecture so basically offers you the
讲座，因此基本上为您提供
whole trust business and this is also
整个信托业务，这也是
why the financial industry starts to get
为什么金融业开始发展
nervous because they're really into
紧张，因为他们真的很喜欢
trust business and now we're comes to
信任企业，现在我们来
technology which promises to solve the
技术有望解决
charge trust thing so how is the more
负责托付的事情，那又如何
organized the to docker containers one
组织到docker容器之一
is holding the ECM client a test RPC is
持有ECM客户端测试RPC
the web 3 interface and the other one is
Web 3界面，另一个是
in PostgreSQL database then there's a
在PostgreSQL数据库中，然后有一个
back-end server it's code which is as
后端服务器的代码是
you see for the web search a library 30
您会在网络上看到图书馆30
BC to access database and some UI layer
BC访问数据库和一些UI层
I try to demo this so let's start to
我尝试演示一下，让我们开始
first year if I just talked to yes you
第一年，如果我刚跟你说过
can see that this is my database
可以看到这是我的数据库
container and this is my my container
容器，这是我的容器
holding the whole test our PC
举行整个测试，我们的电脑
installation so I told me to install
安装，所以我告诉我安装
such as can run this docker image and in
例如可以运行此docker映像并在
one thing here I'm logged in as the
一件事，我以
Munich 3 company and in the other
慕尼黑3公司和其他
browser
浏览器
I'm BMW BMW has some cell deals and
我是宝马宝马有一些单元交易，
mimicry has some ideals you don't see
模仿有一些你看不到的理想
the pile deals because they're still
堆交易，因为他们仍然
here local it says local unpublished so
这里本地它说本地未发布所以
these guys are in the database I can
这些家伙在数据库中，我可以
then say I want these guys to be
然后说我要这些家伙成为
published they're pending so they have
发表他们正在等待，所以他们有
to wait until they're really confirmed
等到他们真的被确认
to this docker container if I go go here
如果我去这里，就到这个码头集装箱
I see now the overview over all the
我现在看到了所有
things and if i refresh
事情，如果我刷新
I can also here to see the overview so
我也可以在这里看到概述
what do we have it's kind of this is the
我们所拥有的是
order book you see that this is kind of
订单簿，您会发现这是一种
sort at work in the middle it tries to
尝试在中间进行排序
be as close as possible this means that
尽可能地接近，这意味着
the interview would like so for two
面试想两个
hundred thousand for this exchange I'd
我想十万
try to sell and mimicry would file but
尝试出售，模仿会提出，但
not for so much or slightly less five
不多于或少五
hundred thousand so there's no match no
十万，所以没有比赛
nothing and what you think and see if if
什么都没有，你怎么想，看看是否
if I'm you'll agree
如果我同意的话
let's switch here I want to have a deal
让我们切换到这里我想达成协议
I have to basically create a new deal
我必须基本上创造一个新协议
and you buy to you and let's say you
你买给你，说你
want to have one hundred thousand and
想要有十万个
here I can get the current exchange
在这里我可以得到最新的交流
right basically it's just looking in the
基本上，它只是看着
order book admitted at which range I
我接受的订单范围
have to to put here in order to make
必须放在这里才能使
sure that there there is a deal now if I
确保如果我现在有协议
switch back here and refresh of course I
切换回这里并刷新我
cannot see anything because
看不到任何东西，因为
again I have to publish this guy first
再次，我必须先发布这个人
and now the software identifies here
现在该软件可以在此处识别
that there is a match here for this new
在这里有一个匹配这个新的
business deal if I if I execute it then
商业交易，如果我执行的话
this part of the deal will be fully
这笔交易的一部分将完全
executed because I can buy 100,000 and
被处决因为我可以买100,000
this cannot be fully executed then this
这不能完全执行然后
number goes down to to 100,000 so I can
数字下降到100,000，所以我可以
execute my order
执行我的订单
and again I have I have no match here so
再说一次，我在这里没有比赛，所以
that's the kind of the demo yeah I'm
那是演示的那种，是的，我是
running out of time for for the demo the
演示用完了
maybe I can show one thing if I'm here
如果我在这里，也许我可以展示一件事
then I can also switch to the docker
然后我也可以切换到docker
container and use the test tree that the
容器并使用测试树
web to need javascript in order to
网络需要javascript才能
verify what I think in the UI that is
验证我在UI中的想法
actually on the blockchain which is
实际上在区块链上
pretty cool
很酷
so if you want to learn more about smart
因此，如果您想进一步了解智能
contracts is here there's a home page
合同在这里有主页
there's a white paper of coffee cereal
有一张咖啡谷物白皮书
there's some good documentation about
有一些关于
the website our script library there's
该网站的脚本库
also a clip scale so we come to the
还有一个夹子秤，所以我们来
summary blockchain internet of trust
摘要信任区块链互联网
yeah that's my time we call your
是的，那是我的时间，我们打电话给你
technology lots of help as well but
技术方面也有很多帮助，但
technology is cool it's a technology for
技术很酷，这是一种技术
unbanked and unbanked or one on the one
没有银行和没有银行或一对一
hand people people they're not allowed
帮别人把他们禁止
to have accounts what unbanked are also
拥有未银行账户
machines so it's also a solution to to
机器，这也是解决
give the authority to accumulate and
授权积累
spend funds to machines which already
花钱到已经有的机器上
has some potential it's an efficient
有潜力，这是一个有效的
classless global exchange of values if
全球无阶级价值交换
you if you have an open under topic
如果您有公开主题
network you could also do private
网络，你也可以做私人
networks but it's a different topic and
网络，但这是一个不同的主题，
it really is pushing distributed
它真的在推动分布式
business models challenges currency
商业模式挑战货币
currently our privacy as Bitcoin and the
目前我们的隐私为比特币和
serum they don't have private
他们没有私人的血清
so everybody sees all the transactions
这样每个人都可以看到所有交易
one the connection between an address
一个地址之间的联系
and the person gets leaked you can go to
和那个人泄漏，你可以去
the full historic database and maybe
完整的历史数据库，也许
find out a lot of things with network
通过网络发现很多东西
analysis this is not always wanted so
分析这并不总是想要的，所以
many of the lock chains now they try to
许多锁链现在他们试图
find new ways to to address privacy in a
寻找解决隐私问题的新方法
sense that you can no longer see where
感觉你再也看不到哪里
the money is coming from but still have
钱来自但仍然有
the Trust's that nobody is funneling the
信任的是，没有人在漏斗
funds into into wrong directions
资金进入错误的方向
another topic is scalability in order to
另一个主题是可扩展性
to be used for mass mass transactions if
用于批量交易
you really want to everybody wants of a
你真的想要每个人都想要一个
coffee with cryptocurrencies some
带有加密货币的咖啡
transactions per second will not do this
每秒交易不会这样做
is also addressed by the various
也由各种
currencies it's it's in development if
货币是否正在开发中
you want another one is energy
你想要另一个是能量
consumption Bitcoin network these days
这些天消费比特币网络
is using as much energy as the country
正在消耗与该国一样多的能源
of Ecuador just to be wrong so this is
厄瓜多尔的人只是错了，所以这是
the proof of work the hashing stuff
工作证明哈希的东西
which is really insane if you think
如果您认为这真的很疯狂
there's another approach which is
还有另一种方法是
probably coming shortly to the Syrian
可能不久就会来到叙利亚
Network which is moving from this proof
从这个证明移动的网络
of work algorithm to proof of stake
算法证明权益
agreement so this means instead of
协议，所以这意味着
calculating hashes there's a set up
计算哈希有​​一个设置
where you say for the mining I put some
你在采矿的地方说我放了一些
money on the side and this is locked
钱在一边，这是锁定的
which gives me the right to do mining
这使我有权进行采矿
basically I promise not to mess up this
基本上我保证不会搞砸
mining which is then not calculated but
挖掘，然后不计算但
more on a class basis if somebody can
如果有人可以的话，在课堂上更多
show that I mess up this mining they
表明我搞砸了他们的采矿
will kill my funds so I as a miner have
会杀死我的资金，所以我作为一名矿工
an incentive to to be trustworthy in
激励人们守信
order not to to kill my funds this is
为了不杀死我的资金，这是
the gist of the proof of stake and this
权益证明的依据
would then basically solve a huge part
然后基本上可以解决很大一部分
of this an economic energy consumption
其中经济能源消耗
another one is maturity
另一个是成熟
even though there's a lot of money
即使有很多钱
Lawtons really really build in its
劳顿真的真的建立在
infancy so there's a lot of topics that
婴儿期，所以有很多话题
not fully addressed that it's not really
没有完全解决，这不是真的
clear what will happen so it's really
清楚会发生什么，所以这真的
really early stage and regulatory well
真的很早期，监管也很好
let's say it's a mess if everybody has a
假设每个人都有一个混乱
different idea about it which heavily
关于它的不同想法
collides is the fact that is really
碰撞的事实是
really simple to set up a global network
建立全球网络非常简单
which does not care about somebody
不在乎某人
telling what you can do what you can not
告诉你可以做什么，你不能做什么
do so there also have to solve this one
这样做那里也必须解决这一问题
okay
好的
[Music]
[音乐]